You video chat with Amy all the time.
How is this different?
(Sheldon:)Don't you like Amy?
- Of course, I like Amy.
- Well, there's the difference.
(Leonard:)Excuse me, that's Priya.
- Hi, Leonard.
- Hey, honey.
- l miss you.
- Oh, I miss you too.
(Sheldon:)I miss the old days...
(Sheldon:)...when your romantic partners
could be returned to the video store.
(Sheldon:)Thanks for letting me stay here while
Leonard Skypes with his girIfriend.
(Penny:)Oh, it's no problem.
(Penny:)It's actually kind of nice.
You reading, me reading.
(Penny:)We're like an old married couple.
(Sheldon:)If we were an old married couple...
(Sheldon:)...the wife would serve iced tea
and snickerdoodles.
(Penny:)I don't have iced tea
(Sheldon:)A good wife would go to the store.
(Penny:)I want a divorce.
(Sheldon:)Good. On the way to see the lawyer,
pick up some tea and cookies.
(Sheldon:)I must say,
I am enjoying your new chair.
- Oh, it's great, isn't it?
- It is.
(Sheldon:)Aligns the lumbar, cradles the coccyx,
balances the buttocks.
(Sheldon:)- This is a chair worthy of the name.
- What name?
(Sheldon:)Chair.
(Penny:)Well, I'm glad you like it.
(Penny:)I mean, I still can't get over the fact
someone just threw it away.
- What?
- It was just sitting on the street.
(Penny:)I paid a homeless guy
to help me get it up here.
(Sheldon(jumps up):)Oh, dear. Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
- What is wrong?
- I've been sitting in garbage.
(Penny:)Sheldon, take it easy.
(Sheldon:)You take it easy.
I need to use your shower.
(Penny:)I went into this marriage
with so much hope.
(Sheldon:)There's a wet Band-Aid
on the shower floor.